http://www.roommaster2000.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy | innQuest Software | Hotel Property Management Software
Menu
HomeProducts & SolutionsProductsroomMasterPowerful, robust, full-featured cloud or server basedroomMaster AnywhereSimple, easy-to-use, next-gen cloud PMSStayfullStay full with our powerful channel managerExceed POSUser friendly, packed with features and fully integrated with roomMaster PMS.SolutionsHotel CRM CloudinnQuest PaymentsMulti-Property ManagementRevenue OptimizationPMS Integrations and InterfacesSmart Hotel and AutomationNEED HELP?Let us help you find the right product for your needsContact usServicesTraining and ConsultingPMS IntegrationRequest a QuoteCompanyAbout UsCareersCase StudiesBlogContact UsClient AreaSupportPrivacy PolicyHome / Privacy PolicyInnQuest Privacy PolicyThis privacy policy sets out how InnQuest Software uses and protects any information that the user provides when visiting or using this website. InnQuest Software is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask the user to provide certain information by which he/she can be identified when using this website; the user can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. InnQuest Software may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. This policy is effective from May 23, 2018.What data do we collect?Many types of data are collected in InnQuest Software site when users register or browse the website.Information you provide:Personal information, including first name, last name, e-mail address, home or work address, phone number, postal or zip code collected to provide the users with access to InnQuest Software site, and get the utmost of the site tools, services, and contents.Financial information, including credit card number, Bank account number, and billing address when the user agrees to pay for a service provided by InnQuest Software. All payments are processed by a third-party provider complying with all industry standards for safety and data protection, and InnQuest Software does not have direct access to your payment information.Information we collect automatically:When you visit our website, some information is automatically collected from devices (mobile, computer, laptop, tablet) used to visit our website or use our booking software, including, but not limited to, operating system, access times, browser information (type, language, and history), settings, and other data about your device that we use to provide the services or as otherwise described in this Policy (“Device Information”). We also collect information about your usage and activity on our website using certain technologies, such as cookies, web beacons and other technologies. This is to help us provide a better / more personalized user experience and service to you.Non-identifiable information:InnQuest Software may share collected information that does not include personal or financial Information as well as may disclose non-Identifying Information and data logs with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling, market segmentation and other statistical purposes. Any information shared in these contexts will never contain any personal or financial Information.How data is used?In order to use the InnQuest Software site, the user is requested to provide certain information. InnQuest Software does not share any of this information with any person or entity, other than as set out in this policy.No other third party receives any information or transactional data, except for those with whom the user has transactions and shares that information.The data we collect is used to improve the InnQuest Software website, to notify consumers about updates to the website and for communications related to customer service. InnQuest Software sends the user a welcome email to verify and activate the account and other transactional emails for operational purposes, such as billing confirmation, accounts management or system and service maintenance. Those emails can be stopped only by terminating the user account which is a user decision.InnQuest Software may also send the user promotion notifications, new service announcements, evaluation surveys to collect productive feedback about the service provided by the website. User can opt out of receiving these email communications from InnQuest Software at any time by unsubscribing or emailing the InnQuest Software admin team at info@innquest.com to have the user profile/information removed from InnQuest Software email list or registration database.Data privacy & securityInnQuest Software does not rent, sell, or share neither personal nor financial Information about users with other people or non-affiliated companies for marketing purposes (including direct marketing purposes) without users’ explicit permission.InnQuest Software owns and controls user information and is committed to protect, maintain and perform all necessary security measures to minimize the risk of abuse, loss, hacking access, disclosure and forceful change & alteration of data.All information collected by InnQuest is stored in our servers located in the United States. Our servers are compliant under the EU-US Privacy Shield. We take all commercially reasonable precautions to ensure that our partners comply with all applicable data protection laws as stated in our user agreement.Your information will be stored for the duration of the contract or for as long as you are using our services. Once the contract is terminated, your information will be deleted, unless we are required to store such information for a given period of time as prescribed by applicable laws.If you want us to amend or delete certain information we hold about you, please contact us at info@innquest.com. Please note that the deletion of your information may prevent you from accessing certain services. We will honour requests for deletion unless required to store certain information in accordance with applicable laws.Links to other websitesInnQuest Software may contain links to enable users to visit other websites of interest. However, once the user has used these links to leave the InnQuest Software site, user should note that InnQuest Software does not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be held responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which the user provides whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. Users should exercise caution and refer to the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.Cookie policyA cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive for variable length of time. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps to improve the browsing experience, provides advanced functionality as well as allows web applications to respond to you as an individual such as simplifying or personalizing log in. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. Unless you are logging in, the cookies are never used by InnQuest Software to identify you personally. And we do not use cookies to provide targeted advertising. To the contrary, cookies help us provide the user with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages the users find useful and which ones they don’t. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.There are different types of Cookies used by InnQuest Software:Session cookies that only last until you leave the website – what is called the end of your browser session. These include the cookies that expand and collapse menus, make the InnQuest Software font page appear properly on your screen.Persistent cookies that are stored in your computer and can last for different lengths of time. Some last 30 minutes, some for a few months, and some last for years. These cookies are used for statistics and analysis to improve our website and tailor it to our customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. Some of those persistent cookies come from third party companies who help us improving our site’s performance, such as Google Analytics.You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.Accessing, amending or deleting your data 500 North Westshore Boulevard, Suite 950 Tampa, FL 33609 1.813.288.4900 info@innquest.com Need Help? Call Us:1.813.288.4900+44 (0) 33 0100 1090+61 3 9728 3755 Subscribe to our newsletter
ProductsProperty management softwareCloud PMSOnline DistributionOnline Booking EnginePoint of SalePMS AddonsSolutionsHotel CRM CloudMulti-Property ManagementRevenue OptimizationPMS Integrations and InterfacesSmart Hotel and AutomationServicesTraining and ConsultingPMS IntegrationCompanyAboutCareersCase StudiesMore LinksMake a PaymentFollow UsCorporate HQ 500 North Westshore Blvd Suite 950 Tampa, Florida 33609 sales@innquest.com +1 813 288 4900EMEA 1 Westleigh Park, Scirocco Close, Moulton Park Northampton, NN3 6BW UK sales@innquestemea.com +44 (0) 33 0100 1090Canada 100 -18236, 105 Ave Edmonton, AB T5S 2R5 Canada sales@canada.innquest.com +1 888 477 0344APAC 55 Belair Rd Kingswood SA 5062 Australia sales@innquest.com +61 3 9728 3755Caribbean 146 Sea Shell Close Long Bay, St. Philip BB18071
Barbados sales@dnsmanagement.net +1 246 423 2049Asia/Fiji 17 Kalimna Grove Minchinbury. NSW. 2770 Australia support@yieldman.freshdesk.com +61 2 8003 4577
Copyright © 2020 InnQuest Software. All rights reserved. |
Terms of Service
|
Privacy Policy
